Hello?
Ladies and gentlemen!
Boys and girls! The Flying Graysons!
Rachel!
The circus again! The boy...
Take a breath. honey. Just calm down.
He watched as his parents fell.
Oh. God. It was... It
was so scary. I felt...
It was just a dream.
Okay. Just... Just breathe
like we practiced. okay?
It's okay. Everything's gonna be okay.
Okay?
Sweetie. you need to get a
little more rest. Come on.
Everything is gonna be okay.
Mom?
Yeah.
Keep the door locked.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
With the low pressure
coming in. we will see
the temperatures dropping.
Which means this rain would then
turn to sleet and possible. even snow.
Detective Grayson. Amy Rohrbach.
Transfer from Oakland.
I'm your new partner.
Right. The Captain mentioned.
It's a pleasure.
I read your file.
You seem to know what you're doing.
You keep doing your thing. I'll
keep doing my thing. We'll be good.
Don't take it personally.
I need a breath mint or something?
He's been pushing off getting a
partner since he got here a month ago.
Some shit about his
last one or something.
He's from Gotham. Likes to work alone.
Gotham?
Jesus...
What happened to his last partner?
Gassed by The Joker. Who knows?
Did you have breakfast?
You shouldn't drink coffee.
You shouldn't smoke.
I quit.
No. you didn't.
Well. I'm going to.
Darn it. I forgot to get cream.
You forgot to get everything.
Okay.
I'm late.
Can you take the bus
to school again today?
Sure.
Okay.
You never sleep anymore.
No. not often.
It's because you're scared of me.
I am not scared of you. honey.
I can tell when you're lying.
I can feel it. You know I can.
Pray with me.
No. no. Talk with me.
What's inside of me? What is it?
Rachel. just please
pray with me. Please!
- Our father who art in...
- No more praying.
No more lying. Tell me
what you're not. Mom!
Tell me!
I'm sorry. Mama.
It's okay. baby!
- Rachel!
- I'm gonna miss the bus.
Rachel!
Hey. kid. You tell your mother
that screaming keeps us
up all hours of the night.
I'm calling the police again.
You hear me? I don't care
about your emotional issues!
Weirdo.
Boo!
Come on. What are you hiding from?
You don't have to be shy with me.
I like freaks.
Leave her alone. Kyle.
Don't you have a touchdown
or something to throw. Matt?
Just leave her alone. asshole.
Before I make you.
Maybe you should take a seat.
Knock him out!
Sit back down! Both of you! Now!
Come on. It was getting good.
- Does it hurt?
- It doesn't hurt.
Slut.
Slut!
Uh. Matt. Thanks for...
Mom?
Mom. I am really sorry
about this morning.
Rachel. That's what she calls you.
But that is not who you are.
Let my mom go.
This woman is not your mother.
Tell her.
Tell her!
I am not your mother.
- But I do love you.
- No.
You have good inside
your heart. sweetheart.
Don't do...
There. Now. that's better.
Pink?
The kids love it.
What was that?
I'm only here for Tyler Hackett.
Leave the drugs. Leave
the guns. And walk away.
Where's Batman?
He could be anywhere. man.
He's up there somewhere.
Look up. Look up.
Oh. where's the Bat! Where is he?
Hey. The little birdie's alone.
Get him!
Tyler! Where you going. man?
If you ever touch your
kid again. I will find you.
Fuck Batman.
Are you guys sure it's him?
Absolutely. Captain.
We called Gotham P.D.
He hasn't been seen for over a year.
Disappeared. they said.
They thought he might be dead.
Why come here? Why Detroit?
The weather?
Let's just hope to hell
he's just passing through.
You know the problems that
these masks bring with 'em.
Painted freaks. Psychopaths in drag.
We don't need that shit.
We got enough of our own
regular problems here.
Come on. guys. Back to work.
I need to talk to you
for a second. Eddie.
Sure. Captain.
Where to?
Detroit. One way. please.
I'll give your compliments to the chef.
My name is Sally. I work here.
First. I don't need to know who you are.
or how you got here. okay?
What I really care about is keeping
girls your age off the streets.
Or out of the adult shelters
which aren't much better.
There's a youth shelter.
a few blocks from here.
They'll have a bed for
you. No questions asked.
Shortcut.
I grew up here. me and this city.
I've lived here since I was your age.
On the streets. too.
Shelters saved my life.
Lies!
She's lying. Look behind you.
Hey. come on.
I've been where you are.
You feel like you can't trust anyone.
What's wrong. sugar?
I was just gonna give you a ride.
Come on. It's okay.
Run!
Rachel!
Wait!
Stop!
Let's go. kid.
Hey. uh. any luck on that Robin thing?
Wait. are you talking to me?
Is everybody else dead?
Because I clearly must be the last
person on Earth for that to happen.
I guess I haven't been
the most welcoming.
Hey. Grayson. You got that
thing for helping kids. right?
Hi. there. How you doing?
Word on the street is
you like playing baseball
with bricks and cop cars.
I am Detective Dick Grayson.
You wanna talk about what happened?
It's you.
- I'm not sure if you...
- You're the boy from the circus.
Please.
Can you help me?
_
Kory Anders.
Hello?
_
Hmm? Hmm?
Who are you?
Is this some kind of
sick practical joke?
I remember.
People were happy that night.
What the hell is this?
You. most of all.
Your parents...
I watched them fall.
You kept wishing it was a dream.
Wishing you would wake up.
Who put you up to this?
Everything led me here.
To you.
It can't be by accident.
You've got to help
me. I don't know how...
You want help? So you
throw a brick at a cop car?
You don't understand...
- Okay. make me understand.
- Someone killed my mom!
Okay. Name. address.
She was all I had.
The only person in the
world who cared for me.
I am alone now.
I want to help you.
Listen. I'm gonna check this out. okay?
Don't leave me here.
Rachel. you vandalized a police car.
- You're not going anywhere.
- You don't understand.
You need to lock me up.
Please.
There is something inside of me.
Something evil.
I can't give you the
kind of help you need.
I will find someone who can.
Don't leave me here.
Look. I'm sorry. I really am.
Hey. so. she's saying
her mom was killed.
If you could send someone
down there. that'll be great.
Okay. I'll call you
if anything checks out.
- Thanks.
- It's probably bullshit though.
Kids down there livin'
on the street stealing...
- The Mayor has...
- They'll say anything to get out of trouble.
...released a warrant demanding the
crime fighting vigilante known as Robin...
Yeah. I know.
...to leave Detroit immediately.
Quote. "This is a violent
sociopath." End quote.
Hey. can I ask you something?
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
So. what? You and your sidekick go bad?
I'm sorry?
Your partner at Gotham P.D.
I mean. I'm no mind reader.
it just seems kinda obvious.
I guess we had different
ideas of how to do the job.
How's that? He on the take?
I heard most of Gotham is.
No. not him.
He was a hero to a lot of people.
Including me.
A stop-at-nothing guy who
solved everything with his fists.
I admired him at first. what he did...
Or was trying to do.
But eventually. I had to walk away.
Why?
Because I was becoming
too much like him.
So. you're not really. huh?
What?
An asshole.
Don't tell. It will kill my rep.
Yeah. Well. your secret's safe with me.
Hey. there.
We're gonna transfer you.
We'll be putting you
in with the other kids.
It will be safer for you there.
It's okay. Bring your bag.
Right this way.
Grayson.
This is Officer Jones.
Traverse City P.D.
- Mm-hmm.
- Girl you called in about. Rachel Roth?
We found her mother. Gunshot to
the head. Looks like a homicide.
I'll have our C.S.I send you
the details as we get them.
Okay. thanks.
Let me kill him!
Let me kill him now!
Detective Grayson. Can I get
a 10-20 on the car number 310?
My dear...
I was worried for you.
Who are you. exactly?
Who am I?
Who the hell are you?
And who do you work for?
Uh. I don't... I don't know. I...
You come here. you sit at my side.
you sleep in my bed!
I trusted you!
And you turn on me?
You betray me?
Because of this girl?
Who is she? What do you want with her?
I don't know.
I woke up in a car. And these
men were trying to kill me...
I loved you.
Oh...
I don't think I loved you too.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure that's a no.
Wait!
Rachel Roth.
You've always known you
were different. haven't you?
That you have a destiny.
Please...
I have been looking for you for so long.
Let me go.
Nothing resembles itself tonight.
This dirty room is a church.
I appear the villain but
in truth. I am the savior.
You...
You pose as the innocent.
but deep inside...
You know you're fecund and damned.
You have the skin of the lamb.
The sheath by which he
will penetrate this world.
and seed its destruction.
But alas. you are the doorway
he would walk through upright
to put out our sun. and I...
Cannot allow that to happen.
I have to save us all.
I will lay your heart
beside the heart of a beast.
And beside the heart of a simpleton.
And burn them all.
And the doorway will be closed forever.
Don't hurt me!
Rachel!
Help! Help!
Rachel. Rachel. open the door!
Rachel! Rachel!
Rachel! Open the door!
Rachel!
What happened?
I don't know!
Please help me!
This is yours?
Family heirloom.
From the circus?
Not the one you're thinking.
Come on. let's go.
Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
My mom
says there's no such thing as monsters.
I think she was wrong.
Okay.
Rad.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --